Cooking non-veg in the month of Sawan is considered a sin.
But why has sister committed this sin
?  So as you know, the month of Sawan is
going on and in this month everyone avoids eating non-veg
food.  And
anyway, no one eats non-veg at my house.  Just
leave me.  But ever since the month of Sawan has started, I have become
fed up of eating pumpkin, potato, bitter gourd etc.
So I told my sister that I cannot eat non-veg.
Make something which is vegetarian
but gives a non-vegetarian feel.   The
fake fish will eat the string.
How is this possible?  As long as I am alive,
everything is possible.
[laughs]
I never thought in my life that a fake
fish could be made.  So what this is, first
boil one potato in hot water for four forts.  Then after boiling everything,
mash it well and add some gram flour,
salt and turmeric to it and make a dough.
After that, see what happened, he
gave it the same shape as a piece of fish and fried it.   I
mean, look at his brain.  Then I
made curry gravy on the side and added all the fried fake
fish to it and made fake
fish curry.  Look at the beast here.  So he
cannot believe that this is a fake fish.
Sometimes fake egg, sometimes fake chicken,
where do you get all these ideas from?  You are thinking
that something should be made of man only.
[screaming sound]
Now let's tell them before mom thinks they're real fish and
beats them both up.